whatspoppin.net 2007-02-19

# WhatsPoppin.net

Whatspoppin.net Privacy Policy  
Whatspoppin.net has drafted this document, which details how we gather and disseminate information, in an effort to demonstrate our strong commitment to online privacy. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy. 

Use of Internet Protocol Address  
We use your Internet protocol (IP) address for several reasons: to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, to help identify you and your shopping cart, and to gather broad demographic information. 

Use of Registration Information  
Our site's registration area requires customers to supply contact information, such as name and e-mail address, and demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, or income level. We use this information to send you promotional materials from our company and from some of our partners. However, users may opt out of ? or opt in to ? these promotional e-mail messages at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) 

Use of Demographic Information  
We also collect demographic and profile data that we use to tailor your experience at YourCompany.com. Based on this information, we display products and content we feel you might interest you. 

Use of Order Information  
When you place an order, Whatspoppin.net requests information such as contact information, Social Security number, credit card number and demographic information. The contact information you provide is used to send you orders, company information and promotional material from our partners. You can opt out or opt in at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) 

Your financial information is used for the sole purpose of billing you for products and services. You Social Security number is used to identify you, and demographic data is collected to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel would interest you most. 

Use of Online Survey Information  
To participate in our online surveys, you will be required to supply contact and demographic information. Whatspoppin.net uses this data to send you information about the company. We might use this information to contact you as necessary. However, you may opt out of or opt in to our mailings at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site and used to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel would most interest you. 

Use of Information Collected in Contests  
To participate in our contests, you will be required to supply contact and demographic information. Whatspoppin.net uses this data to send you information about the company. We might use this information to contact you as necessary. However, you may opt out of or opt in to our mailings at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) Demographic and profile data are collected at our site and used to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel you would most interest you. 

Public Forums Guidelines  
Whatspoppin.net offers chat rooms and bulletin boards. Please note that information that is disclosed in these arenas becomes public. Use caution in disclosing any personal information. 

Security  
Whatspoppin.net features security measures (elaborate about your site's security measures here) to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information placed under our control. 

Children's Guidelines  
We do not collect or use any online contact information or identifiable off-line contact information about a child without parental consent. We do not distribute personally identifiable information about children without parental consent. We do not give children the ability to post or distribute personal information without prior consent. We do not entice children with games or contests that would encourage them to disclose personal information. 

Opt Out/Opt In  
Whatspoppin.net allows users to opt out of receiving e-mail from us or our partners. To opt out of our mailing list you can send e-mail to a remove mailing list. 

Correct/Update Personal Information  
Whatspoppin.net allows you to change or modify your personal information by sending e-mail to a remove e-mail address or by visiting a designated customer service page. 

Disclaimer  
This site contains links to other sites. Whatspoppin.net is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites. 

Contact Us  
If you have any additional questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us: 

Whatspoppin.net
